Well, that's it. Those are all the fundamentals you need to know, the basics to get started with
some ex-unit stuff and some integration testing stuff. We're gonna go deeper, but before we do,
the next section I want to remind you is an optional section for those who want to get
more familiar with different types of accessions and testing different values. It was actually a
section from the unit testing course which is provided here for free for everyone. It is not
part of the price you paid to buy this course. It will introduce you to fluent accessions,
it will show you how you can assert different things and you can apply that knowledge for
integration tests. If you're already familiar with that, you can just skip it. It is technically
optional. Like I said in the beginning of the section, you can find the code for the section
you just watched below this video.